A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1958-1970 FA400
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1966
  - Norway, 1966/767
    - C-L (Reel 54, Frame 774)
  - Iran, 1966/771
    - A-U (Reel 54, Frame 782)
    - Iran - Nursing, 1966/771.C
      - Nemazee School of Nursing (Reel 54, Frame 803)
  - Portugal, 1966/773
    - A-B (Reel 54, Frame 806)
    - Portugal - Nursing, 1966/773.C
      - School of Nursing (Reel 54, Frame 815)
  - Romania, 1966/783
    - B-R (Reel 54, Frame 825)
  - Russia, 1966/785
    - Voznesensky, Andrei (Reel 54, Frame 836)
  - Finland, 1966/787
    - S-U (Reel 54, Frame 839)
    - Finland - Nursing, 1966/787.C
      - Helsinki College of Nursing (Reel 54, Frame 853)
  - Poland, 1966/789
    - A-Z (Reel 54, Frame 862)
    - Poland - Nursing, 1966/789.C
      - Poland - Nursing (Reel 54, Frame 904)
  - Spain, 1966/795
    - M-U (Reel 54, Frame 909)
    - Spain - Medical Sciences, 1966/795.A
      - University of Navarra (Medical School) (Reel 54, Frame 923)
  - Sweden, 1966/800
    - C-Z (Reel 54, Frame 927)
  - Switzerland, 1966/803
    - C-W (Reel 54, Frame 1054)
  - Turkey, 1966/805
    - A-W (Reel 54, Frame 1109)
  - Egypt, 1966/812
    - A-U (Reel 55, Frame 1)
    - Egypt - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1966/812.D
      - A-U (Reel 55, Frame 32)
    - Egypt - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1966/812.E
      - A-K (Reel 55, Frame 37)
  - Jordan, 1966/816
    - Majaj, Amin S. (Reel 55, Frame 45)
  - Saudi Arabia and Oman, 1966/817
    - Azmeh, Ahmad A. (Reel 55, Frame 47)
  - Israel, 1966/825
    - Yaron, Dan (Reel 55, Frame 56)
    - A-Z (Reel 55, Frame 237)
  - Lebanon, 1966/833
    - A-L (Reel 55, Frame 304)
    - Lebanon - Medical Sciences, 1966/833.A
      - American University of Beirut (Reel 55, Frame 382)
    - Lebanon - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1966/833.E
      - Haj, Sabbah Al (Reel 55, Frame 385)
  - General Program and Policy, 1966/900
    - Administration (Reel 55, Frame 388)
    - Art Purchases (Reel 55, Frame 397)
  - Members and Meetings, 1966/903
    - Bingham, Barry (Reel 55, Frame 409)
    - Brace, Lloyd D. (Reel 55, Frame 437)
    - Bunche, Ralph J. (Reel 55, Frame 445)
    - Coggeshall, Lowell T. (Reel 55, Frame 458)
    - Dickey, John S. (Reel 55, Frame 484)
    - Dillon, C. Douglas (Reel 55, Frame 498)
    - DuBridge, Lee A. (Reel 55, Frame 508)
    - Ebert, Robert H. (Reel 55, Frame 517)
    - Franks of Headington, Oliver Shewell, Baron (Reel 55, Frame 529)
    - Goheen, Robert F. (Reel 55, Frame 541)
    - Hardin, Clifford M. (Reel 55, Frame 554)
    - Hesburgh, Theodore M. (Reel 55, Frame 564)
    - Houghton, Arthur A., Jr. (Reel 55, Frame 635)
    - Kerr, Clark (Reel 55, Frame 640)
    - Kimberly, John R. (Reel 55, Frame 645)
    - Rockefeller, John D. 3rd (Reel 55, Frame 651)
    - Seitz, Frederick (Reel 55, Frame 790)
    - Stanton, Frank (Reel 55, Frame 815)
    - Watson, Thomas J., Jr. (Reel 55, Frame 832)
    - Wood, W. Barry, Jr. (Reel 55, Frame 850)
    - Woods, George D. (Reel 55, Frame 860)
  - Humanities, 1966/911
    - Creative Writing Advisory Committee (B-W) (Reel 55, Frame 867)
  - Agriculture, 1966/923
    - Consultants (A-R) (Reel 55, Frame 964)
- General Correspondence, 1967
  - International, 1967/100
    - Aitken, Thomas H. G. (Reel 1, Frame 1)
    - Allen, LeRoy R. (Reel 1, Frame 210)
    - Anderson, R. Glenn (Reel 1, Frame 290)
    - Arragon, Reginald F. (Reel 1, Frame 359)
    - Baird, Guy B. (Reel 1, Frame 439)
    - Baskett, Ronald S. (Reel 1, Frame 491)
    - Bjork, Kenneth O. (Reel 1, Frame 527)
    - Borlaug, Norman E. (Reel 1, Frame 663)
    - Boshell, Jorge (Reel 1, Frame 731)
    - Bourne, Leo F. (Reel 1, Frame 761)
    - Bradfield, Richard (Reel 1, Frame 795)
    - Brooks, Glenn E. (Reel 1, Frame 1006)
    - Bryant, John H. (Reel 1, Frame 1068)
    - Byrnes, Francis C. (Reel 2, Frame 1)
    - Cameron, Rondo E. (Reel 2, Frame 141)
    - Carey, Donald E. (Reel 2, Frame 201)
    - Causey, Ottis R. (Reel 2, Frame 286)
    - Consultant (Carter, Altice S.) (Reel 2, Frame 332)
    - Consultant (Coleman, James S.) (Reel 2, Frame 382)
    - Consultant (Dunn, Oliver C.) (Reel 2, Frame 492)
    - Consultant (Fletcher, Donald G.) (Reel 2, Frame 549)
    - Consultant (Ingles, Thelma) (Reel 2, Frame 642)
    - Consultant (Maxwell, W. David) (Reel 2, Frame 729)
    - Consultant (Stakman, Elvin C.) (Reel 2, Frame 760)
    - Consultant (Stifel, Laurence D.) (Reel 2, Frame 804)
    - Consultants (C-L) (Reel 2, Frame 839)
    - Consultants (M-W) (Reel 2, Frame 904)
    - Cummings, Ralph W. (Reel 2, Frame 931)
    - Daniel, James M. (Reel 2, Frame 993)
    - Diplomatic Services (A-W) (Reel 3, Frame 1)
    - Duff, Ernest A. (Reel 3, Frame 221)
    - Fitchett, Delbert A. (Reel 3, Frame 263)
    - Germino, Dante (Reel 3, Frame 381)
    - Goldschmidt, Maure L. (Reel 3, Frame 496)
    - Hopper, W. David (Reel 3, Frame 558)
    - Hotels (Caribee) (Reel 3, Frame 712)
    - International (A-I) (Reel 3, Frame 714)
    - International (L-Y) (Reel 3, Frame 955)
    - Johnson, Glenn L. (Reel 4, Frame 1)
    - Jordan, Peter (Reel 4, Frame 211)
    - MacKenzie, Ronald B. (Reel 4, Frame 403)
    - MacLellan, Neil B. (Reel 4, Frame 465)
    - Maner, Jerome H. (Reel 4, Frame 523)
    - Massell, Benton F. (Reel 4, Frame 610)
    - McClung, A. Colin (Reel 4, Frame 643)
    - McKelvey, John J., Jr. (Reel 4, Frame 680)
    - Mead, Donald C. (Reel 4, Frame 706)
    - Miller, Robert W. (Reel 4, Frame 738)
    - Moomaw, James C. (Reel 4, Frame 768)
    - Moore, John W. (Reel 4, Frame 784)
    - Moore, Ward W. (Reel 4, Frame 793)
    - Murphy, Carter (Reel 4, Frame 808)
    - Myren, Delbert T. (Reel 4, Frame 845)
    - Nickel, John L. (Reel 4, Frame 931)
    - Niederhauser, John S. (Reel 4, Frame 1008)
    - North Atlantic Treaty Organization (Brosio, Manlio) (Reel 5, Frame 1)
    - Olson, James A. (Reel 5, Frame 6)
    - Owens, Patrick N. (Reel 5, Frame 67)
    - Quick, James S. (Reel 5, Frame 171)
    - Rachie, Kenneth O. (Reel 5, Frame 190)
    - Randall, Frederick F. (Reel 5, Frame 422)
    - Renfro, Bobby L. (Reel 5, Frame 459)
    - Trant, Gerald I. (Reel 5, Frame 524)
    - United Nations, Food and Agriculture Organization (A-W) (Reel 5, Frame 618)
    - United Nations, World Health Organization (A-W) (Reel 5, Frame 840)
    - United Nations (B-H) (Reel 5, Frame 937)
    - United Nations (I-P) (Reel 6, Frame 1)
    - United Nations (Q-T) (Reel 6, Frame 124)
    - United Nations Economic and Social Council (Reel 6, Frame 286)
    - United Nations Educational Scientific and Cultural Organization (M-S) (Reel 6, Frame 300)
    - Welsch, Delane E. (Reel 6, Frame 353)
    - Woodall, John P. (Reel 6, Frame 443)
    - Wortman, L. Sterling (Reel 6, Frame 498)
    - Wray, Joe D. (Reel 6, Frame 653)
    - Wright, Bill C. (Reel 6, Frame 725)
    - Young, William R. (Reel 6, Frame 762)
    - A (Reel 6, Frame 858)
    - Ba-Bo (Reel 6, Frame 978)
    - Br-Bu (Reel 7, Frame 1)
    - Ca (Reel 7, Frame 127)
    - Ch-Cu (Reel 7, Frame 223)
    - D (Reel 7, Frame 371)
    - E (Reel 7, Frame 478)
    - F (Reel 7, Frame 521)
    - Ga-Gi (Reel 7, Frame 615)
    - Go-Gr (Reel 7, Frame 744)
    - Ha (Reel 7, Frame 902)
    - He-Ho (Reel 8, Frame 1)
    - I (Reel 8, Frame 100)
    - Ja-Je (Reel 8, Frame 156)
    - Jo-Ju (Reel 8, Frame 261)
    - K (Reel 8, Frame 527)
    - L (Reel 8, Frame 634)
    - Ma (Reel 8, Frame 919)
    - Me-My (Reel 8, Frame 981)
    - O (Reel 9, Frame 1)
    - P (Reel 9, Frame 80)
    - Ra-Ri (Reel 9, Frame 228)
    - Rob-Rog (Reel 9, Frame 367)
    - Roo-Ru (Reel 9, Frame 547)
    - Sa-Sm (Reel 9, Frame 726)
    - Sp-Sw (Reel 9, Frame 948)
    - T (Reel 10, Frame 1)
    - U (Reel 10, Frame 205)
    - V (Reel 10, Frame 255)
    - W (Reel 10, Frame 331)
    - International - Medical Sciences, 1967/100.A
      - World Council of Churches (Christian Medical Commission) (Reel 10, Frame 474)
    - International - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1967/100.E
      - International - Fellowships (Reel 10, Frame 499)
    - International - Virus Studies, 1967/100.V
      - United Nations (World Health Organization) (Reel 10, Frame 528)
  - Applications for Employment, 1967/101
    - S (Reel 10, Frame 532)
  - International Organizations, 1967/103
    - Theatre Criticism (Conference) (Reel 10, Frame 535)
  - United States, 1967/200
    - Aa-Ae (Reel 10, Frame 559)
    - African-American Institute, Inc. (D-N) (Reel 10, Frame 740)
    - African Studies Association (Reel 10, Frame 1008)
    - Agricultural Development Council, Inc. (M-W) (Reel 10, Frame 1087)
    - Alderson-Broaddus College (Music) (Reel 11, Frame 1)
    - Ag-Al (Reel 11, Frame 124)
    - American (A-B) (Reel 11, Frame 288)
    - American Conservatory Theatre (Reel 11, Frame 529)
    - American Council on Education (Africa Committee) (Reel 11, Frame 717)
    - American (C ) (Reel 11, Frame 826)
    - American (E-F) (Reel 11, Frame 978)
    - American Institute (B-R) (Reel 12, Frame 1)
    - American (G-L) (Reel 12, Frame 132)
    - American (M) (Reel 12, Frame 221)
    - American (N-P) (Reel 12, Frame 297)
    - American (S) (Reel 12, Frame 385)
    - American (U) (Reel 12, Frame 528)
    - Am-Ar (Reel 12, Frame 574)
    - Asia (F-S) (Reel 12, Frame 699)
    - Association (A) (Reel 12, Frame 893)
    - Association (B-S) (Reel 12, Frame 1026)
    - As (Reel 13, Frame 1)
    - At-Ay (Reel 13, Frame 249)
    - Ba (Reel 13, Frame 398)
    - Be-Bl (Reel 13, Frame 601)
    - Bo (Reel 13, Frame 915)
    - Brookings Institution (G-O) (Reel 14, Frame 1)
    - Br (Reel 14, Frame 169)
    - Bu (Reel 14, Frame 267)
    - California Institute of Technology (E-T) (Reel 14, Frame 354)
    - Cad-Cam (Reel 14, Frame 415)
    - Carnegie Corporation (M-S) (Reel 14, Frame 643)
    - Car-Caz (Reel 14, Frame 734)
    - Chicago (E-S) (Reel 14, Frame 969)
    - Chicago Symphony Orchestra (Reel 14, Frame 978)
    - Chicago Urban League (Reel 14, Frame 993)
    - Ce-Ch (Reel 15, Frame 1)
    - Ci-Cl (Reel 15, Frame 189)
    - Colgate University, Creative Arts (Supplementary Material) (Reel 15, Frame 381)
    - Columbia University (Rustow, Dankwart A.) (Reel 15, Frame 597)
    - Columbia University (A-W) (Reel 15, Frame 787)
    - Col (Reel 15, Frame 962)
    - Com (Reel 15, Frame 1135)
    - Connecticut (A-T) (Reel 16, Frame 1)
    - Consortium for Nigerian Rural Development (Reel 16, Frame 165)
    - Con (Reel 16, Frame 298)
    - Cornell University (B-E) (Reel 16, Frame 392)
    - Cornell University (F-M) (Reel 16, Frame 551)
    - Cornell University (P-S) (Reel 16, Frame 809)
    - Cornell University (T-W) (Reel 16, Frame 858)
    - Council (A-G) (Reel 16, Frame 1013)
    - Council (H-S) (Reel 17, Frame 1)
    - Coo-Cox (Reel 17, Frame 142)
    - Cr-Cu (Reel 17, Frame 319)
    - Da (Reel 17, Frame 444)
    - Dea-Dek (Reel 17, Frame 521)
    - Del-Dew (Reel 17, Frame 685)
    - Di-Dr (Reel 17, Frame 884)
    - Du (Reel 17, Frame 980)
    - Education and World Affairs (Sharpe, Richard) (Reel 18, Frame 1)
    - Education and World Affairs (H-S) (Reel 18, Frame 121)
    - E-Ed (Reel 18, Frame 517)
    - El-Ex (Reel 18, Frame 650)
    - Fa-Fe (Reel 18, Frame 896)
    - Fi (Reel 19, Frame 1)
    - Fle (Reel 19, Frame 246)
    - Florida Atlantic University (Aquatic Weed Control) (Reel 19, Frame 360)
    - Florida (C-S) (Reel 19, Frame 518)
    - Ford Foundation (A-G) (Reel 19, Frame 640)
    - Ford Foundation (H-L) (Reel 19, Frame 858)
    - Ford Foundation (Swayzee, Cleon O.) (Reel 19, Frame 1003)
    - Ford Foundation (M-W) (Reel 20, Frame 1)
    - Fol-For (Reel 20, Frame 156)
    - Fou-Fow (Reel 20, Frame 431)
    - Fr-Fu (Reel 20, Frame 649)
    - Ga-Ge (Reel 20, Frame 897)
    - Gi-Go (Reel 21, Frame 1)
    - Gr-Gu (Reel 21, Frame 173)
    - Haa-Han (Reel 21, Frame 417)
    - Harvard University (A-G) (Reel 21, Frame 506)
    - Harvard University (H-W) (Reel 21, Frame 649)
    - Har (Reel 21, Frame 823)
    - Has-How (Reel 21, Frame 984)
    - Hu-Hv (Reel 22, Frame 1)
    - Indiana University (A-T) (Reel 22, Frame 133)
    - Institute (A-I) (Reel 22, Frame 261)
    - Institute (P-S) (Reel 22, Frame 483)
    - International (B-R) (Reel 22, Frame 538)
    - Ib-In (Reel 22, Frame 786)
    - Io-Iv (Reel 22, Frame 939)
    - Johns Hopkins University, School of Advanced International Studies (F-O) (Reel 22, Frame 1059)
    - Johns Hopkins University (F-W) (Reel 23, Frame 1)
    - J (Reel 23, Frame 201)
    - K-Ka (Reel 23, Frame 343)
    - Ke (Reel 23, Frame 648)
    - Ki-Ku (Reel 23, Frame 744)
    - La (Reel 23, Frame 841)
    - Le (Reel 23, Frame 963)
    - Lincoln Center (Reel 24, Frame 1)
    - Li (Reel 24, Frame 254)
    - Louisiana State University (Cellulose Wastes) (Reel 24, Frame 423)
    - Louisiana State University (E-S) (Reel 24, Frame 581)
    - Lo-Ly (Reel 24, Frame 640)
    - Macy Foundation (N-P) (Reel 24, Frame 767)
    - Mac-Mag (Reel 24, Frame 957)
    - Mah-Mar (Reel 25, Frame 1)
    - Mas-May (Reel 25, Frame 203)
    - Mc (Reel 25, Frame 316)
    - Me (Reel 25, Frame 390)
    - Michigan State University (Donahue, Roy L.) (Reel 25, Frame 503)
    - Michigan State University (A-I) (Reel 25, Frame 624)
    - Michigan State University (Ries, S. K.) (Reel 25, Frame 717)
    - Michigan State University (Thai Education Conference) (Reel 25, Frame 814)
    - Michigan State University (L-W) (Reel 25, Frame 1002)
    - Mia-Mil (Reel 26, Frame 1)
    - Min-Mit (Reel 26, Frame 220)
    - Morningside College (A-M) (Reel 26, Frame 300)
    - Mo (Reel 26, Frame 407)
    - Mu-My (Reel 26, Frame 695)
    - National Academy of Sciences (African Conference) (Reel 26, Frame 860)
    - National Academy of Sciences (A-V) (Reel 27, Frame 1)
    - National (A) (Reel 27, Frame 339)
    - National (B) (Reel 27, Frame 433)
    - National (C ) (Reel 27, Frame 460)
    - National (D-E) (Reel 27, Frame 671)
    - National (F-G) (Reel 27, Frame 869)
    - National (H-I) (Reel 27, Frame 1058)
    - National (L-R) (Reel 28, Frame 1)
    - National (S-W) (Reel 28, Frame 280)
    - Nah-Nei (Reel 28, Frame 515)
    - New (C-E) (Reel 28, Frame 638)
    - New (J-S) (Reel 28, Frame 748)
    - New York (A-T) (Reel 28, Frame 882)
    - New York (U-Z) (Reel 28, Frame 1057)
    - Newspapers (A-N) (Reel 29, Frame 1)
    - Nel-New (Reel 29, Frame 24)
    - North Carolina (Education) (Reel 29, Frame 39)
    - North Carolina State University (A-S) (Reel 29, Frame 98)
    - Northwestern University (A-W) (Reel 29, Frame 147)
    - Ni-No (Reel 29, Frame 262)
    - Nu (Reel 29, Frame 560)
    - Oak Ridge National Laboratory (Nuclear Desalination) (Reel 29, Frame 664)
    - Oak Ridge National Laboratory (H-Y) (Reel 29, Frame 797)
    - Office of Economic Opportunity (J-M) (Reel 29, Frame 913)
    - Oa-Of (Reel 29, Frame 920)
    - Oh-Ok (Reel 30, Frame 1)
    - Ol-Ov (Reel 30, Frame 175)
    - Pan American (D-H) (Reel 30, Frame 459)
    - Pan American Union (A-S) (Reel 30, Frame 773)
    - Pa (Reel 30, Frame 1001)
    - Pennsylvania State University (B-Z) (Reel 31, Frame 1)
    - Pe (Reel 31, Frame 177)
    - Ph (Reel 31, Frame 376)
    - Pi-Pl (Reel 31, Frame 436)
    - Poe-Poo (Reel 31, Frame 560)
    - Pop (Reel 31, Frame 657)
    - Por-Pow (Reel 31, Frame 833)
    - Princeton University (C-G) (Reel 31, Frame 915)
    - Princeton University (McAlister, John T., Jr.) (Reel 32, Frame 1)
    - Princeton University (M-Y) (Reel 32, Frame 222)
    - Pr (Reel 32, Frame 275)
    - Pu-Py (Reel 32, Frame 524)
    - Q (Reel 32, Frame 746)
    - Ra (Reel 32, Frame 786)
    - Re (Reel 32, Frame 920)
    - Ri-Ro (Reel 33, Frame 1)
    - Ru (Reel 33, Frame 285)
    - Sa (Reel 33, Frame 472)
    - Sc (Reel 33, Frame 777)
    - Se (Reel 33, Frame 885)
    - Sh (Reel 34, Frame 1)
    - Si-Sk (Reel 34, Frame 115)
    - Sloan Foundation (C-W) (Reel 34, Frame 182)
    - Sm (Reel 34, Frame 204)
    - Soc-Sor (Reel 34, Frame 386)
    - Southern (C-R) (Reel 34, Frame 497)
    - Sou (Reel 34, Frame 602)
    - Sp (Reel 34, Frame 821)
    - Stanford (I-U) (Reel 34, Frame 929)
    - Sta (Reel 34, Frame 1109)
    - Ste (Reel 35, Frame 1)
    - Sti-Sty (Reel 35, Frame 90)
    - Su-Sy (Reel 35, Frame 145)
    - Ta (Reel 35, Frame 305)
    - Te (Reel 35, Frame 341)
    - Theatre (A-W) (Reel 35, Frame 410)
    - Th (Reel 35, Frame 625)
    - Ti-Tr (Reel 35, Frame 885)
    - Twentieth Century Fund (B-M) (Reel 36, Frame 1)
    - Ts-Ty (Reel 36, Frame 194)
    - United States, Agency for International Development (A-C) (Reel 36, Frame 335)
    - United States, Agency for International Development (D-I) (Reel 36, Frame 436)
    - United States, Agency for International Development (J-L) (Reel 36, Frame 550)
    - United States, Agency for International Development (M-O) (Reel 36, Frame 625)
    - United States, Agency for International Development (P-R) (Reel 36, Frame 729)
    - United States, Agency for International Development (S-Y) (Reel 36, Frame 855)
    - United States, Agriculture (A-F) (Reel 36, Frame 951)
    - United States, Agriculture (Mehren, George) (Reel 37, Frame 1)
    - United States, Agriculture (G-Z) (Reel 37, Frame 151)
    - United States, Health Education and Welfare (Education) (Reel 37, Frame 347)
    - United States, Health Education and Welfare (A-M) (Reel 37, Frame 638)
    - United States (A-H) (Reel 37, Frame 711)
    - United States, State (A-W) (Reel 37, Frame 819)
    - United States (I-S) (Reel 37, Frame 1091)
    - United States Committee to Further American Contemporary Music (Reel 38, Frame 1)
    - United States Information Agency (F-V) (Reel 38, Frame 3)
    - United States-Japan Cooperative Medical Science Program (Virus Diseases) (Reel 38, Frame 20)
    - United States Junior Chamber of Commerce (Reel 38, Frame 39)
    - United States National Student Association (Reel 38, Frame 43)
    - United States Navigation Company, Inc. (Reel 38, Frame 57)
    - United States Rubber Company (Reel 38, Frame 59)
    - United States Science Task Force for Latin America (Reel 38, Frame 85)
    - United States-South Africa Leader Exchange Program (Reel 38, Frame 89)
    - United States Steel Foundation (Reel 38, Frame 147)
    - University of Arizona (Agricultural Economics) (Reel 38, Frame 193)
    - University of Arizona (D-Y) (Reel 38, Frame 396)
    - University of California (A-G) (Reel 38, Frame 447)
    - University of California (Hardin, Charles M.) (Reel 38, Frame 710)
    - University of California (H-L) (Reel 38, Frame 977)
    - University of California (M-R) (Reel 39, Frame 1)
    - University of California (S-W) (Reel 39, Frame 161)
    - University of Chicago (A-Z) (Reel 39, Frame 360)
    - University of Colorado (B-U) (Reel 39, Frame 585)
    - University (A-C) (Reel 39, Frame 685)
    - University (D) (Reel 39, Frame 778)
    - University (F-G) (Reel 39, Frame 1055)
    - University (H) (Reel 40, Frame 1)
    - University of Illinois (A-F) (Reel 40, Frame 128)
    - University of Illinois (Krannert Center) (Reel 40, Frame 371)
    - University of Illinois (G-L) (Reel 40, Frame 528)
    - University of Illinois (Propp, Kathleen) (Reel 40, Frame 617)
    - University of Illinois (M-V) (Reel 40, Frame 734)
    - University (I-L) (Reel 40, Frame 897)
    - University of Michigan (A-Z) (Reel 40, Frame 1012)
    - University of Minnesota (A-H) (Reel 41, Frame 1)
    - University of Minnesota (L-W) (Reel 41, Frame 94)
    - University of Missouri (B-W) (Reel 41, Frame 216)
    - University (M) (Reel 41, Frame 423)
    - University of Nebraska (C-N) (Reel 41, Frame 525)
    - University (Ne) (Reel 41, Frame 722)
    - University of North Carolina (B-W) (Reel 41, Frame 865)
    - University (No-O) (Reel 41, Frame 952)
    - University of Pennsylvania (A-V) (Reel 42, Frame 1)
    - University of Pittsburgh (C-W) (Reel 42, Frame 205)
    - University ( R) (Reel 42, Frame 406)
    - University (S) (Reel 42, Frame 442)
    - University of Tennessee (C-L) (Reel 42, Frame 620)
    - University of Texas (Population) (Reel 42, Frame 637)
    - University of Texas (B-R) (Reel 42, Frame 786)
    - University of Washington (A-W) (Reel 42, Frame 925)
    - University of Wisconsin (A-E) (Reel 42, Frame 1087)
    - University of Wisconsin (H-K) (Reel 43, Frame 1)
    - University of Wisconsin (M-Y) (Reel 43, Frame 136)
    - University (U-W) (Reel 43, Frame 294)
    - Ug-Un (Reel 43, Frame 407)
    - Up-Ut (Reel 43, Frame 537)
    - Va-Ve (Reel 43, Frame 715)
    - Virginia Polytechnic Institute (B-H) (Reel 43, Frame 761)
    - Vi-Vo (Reel 43, Frame 804)
    - Wac-War (Reel 44, Frame 1)
    - Was (Reel 44, Frame 97)
    - Wat-Way (Reel 44, Frame 293)
    - We (Reel 44, Frame 334)
    - Wh-Wi (Reel 44, Frame 580)
    - Wo-Wy (Reel 44, Frame 763)
    - Xerox ( C ) (Reel 44, Frame 924)
    - Yale University (B-M) (Reel 44, Frame 936)
    - Yale University (P-W) (Reel 45, Frame 1)
    - Y (Reel 45, Frame 188)
    - Z (Reel 45, Frame 280)
    - United States - Medical Sciences, 1967/200.A
      - B-M (Reel 45, Frame 307)
      - T-Y (Reel 45, Frame 449)
    - United States - Nursing, 1967/200.C
      - B-Y (Reel 45, Frame 578)
    - United States - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1967/200.D
      - A-U (Reel 45, Frame 625)
    - United States - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1967/200.E
      - A-M (Reel 45, Frame 764)
      - N-Z (Reel 45, Frame 1025)
    - United States - Humanities and Arts, 1967/200.R
      - Playwrights (B-K) (Reel 46, Frame 1)
      - Playwrights (L-W) (Reel 46, Frame 82)
      - A-U (Reel 46, Frame 172)
    - United States - Social Sciences, 1967/200.S
      - C-W (Reel 46, Frame 223)
    - United States - Virus Studies, 1967/200.V
      - American Committee on Arthropod-borne Viruses (Reel 46, Frame 340)
      - American Committee on Arthropod-borne Viruses (Supplementary Material) (Reel 46, Frame 351)
  - Philippines, 1967/242
    - Administration (January-July) (Reel 45, Frame 356)
    - Administration (August-December) (Reel 45, Frame 459)
    - A (Reel 45, Frame 568)
    - B-K (Reel 45, Frame 714)
    - United States Workshop on Marine Sciences (Reel 45, Frame 819)
    - University of the Philippines (Admissions and Testing) (Reel 47, Frame 1)
    - University of the Philippines (A-N) (Reel 47, Frame 173)
    - University of the Philippines (P-V) (Reel 47, Frame 394)
    - L-Z (Reel 47, Frame 560)
    - Philippines - Medical Sciences, 1967/242.A
      - University (P-S) (Reel 47, Frame 717)
    - Philippines - Nursing, 1967/242.C
      - University of the Philippines (Nursing School) (Reel 47, Frame 775)
    - Philippines - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1967/242.D
      - I-U (Reel 47, Frame 779)
    - Philippines - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1967/242.E
      - Philippines (Reel 47, Frame 844)
      - A-S (Reel 47, Frame 880)
    - Philippines - Humanities and Arts, 1967/242.R
      - University of the Philippines (L-R) (Reel 48, Frame 1)
  - Puerto Rico, 1967/243
    - F-U (Reel 48, Frame 226)
    - Puerto Rico - Medical Sciences, 1967/243.A
      - University of Puerto Rico (Medical School) (Reel 48, Frame 268)
  - Samoa, 1967/245
    - Economic Development (Gerakas, Andrew) (Reel 48, Frame 272)
  - South America and Central America, 1967/300
    - Administration (Reel 48, Frame 280)
    - Inter-American Institute of Agricultural Sciences (A-S) (Reel 48, Frame 447)
    - Inter-American (A-P) (Reel 48, Frame 707)
    - B-P (Reel 48, Frame 966)
    - South America and Central America - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1967/300.D
      - Central American Cooperative Program for Food Improvement (Salazar) (Reel 48, Frame 1110)
      - Central American Cooperative Program for Food Improvement (Supplementary Material) (Reel 49, Frame 1)
  - Argentina, 1967/301
    - A-U (Reel 49, Frame 113)
    - Argentina - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1967/301.E
      - A-M (Reel 49, Frame 343)
    - Argentina - Virus Studies, 1967/301.V